question_data = [{'category': 'History', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'question': 'The Cold War ended with Joseph Stalin&#039;s death.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'category': 'General Knowledge', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'hard', 'question': 'This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'question': 'In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'category': 'History', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'question': 'Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'question': 'The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'question': 'Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'category': 'History', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'question': 'United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'category': 'Science: Mathematics', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'question': 'The sum of any two odd integers is odd.', 'correct_answer': 'False', 'incorrect_answers': ['True']}, {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'easy', 'question': 'In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}, {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games', 'type': 'boolean', 'difficulty': 'medium', 'question': 'In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.', 'correct_answer': 'True', 'incorrect_answers': ['False']}]